about-australia.com 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Australia's Guide

Menu

Search

## Australias.guide – Privacy Policy

Australias Guide Pty. Ltd. (referred to as Australias.guide) manage and maintain an internet web portal which provides Travel & Tourism information about Australia and related Australian businesses.

Australias.guide recognises the importance of client privacy and support best practice procedures in the way your personal information is handled.

By providing your personal information you agree and consent to the collection, use, disclosure, storage and holding of your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Privacy Compliance

This privacy policy statement has been made in accordance with amendments to the Federal Government Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000 (New Privacy Laws) which took effect from 21 December 2001 as well as the Spam Act 2003 which took effect from 10 April 2004.  
The National Privacy Principles can be obtained through the website of the office of the Federal Privacy Commissioner (http://www.privacy.gov.au).

### Information collected by Australias.guide

Australias.guide collects information from users, which may include personal Information, at different points on our website as follows: When you visit our website, our server makes a record of your visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes:

– Your server IP address  
– Your top level domain (for example .com, .gov, .net .au, etc.)  
– The pages you accessed and the documents downloaded  
– The date and time of your visit to the site  
– The previous site you have visited  
– The type of browser you are using

From time to time we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies may use information (not personal or contact details) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

### How we use cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that a website can store on your computer’s hard drive. They allow us to recognise you when you return to our site. When you visit Australias.guide, create a user account, download or purchase a product from us, or sign-in to your advertising account we may set cookies on your personal computer.

We require that cookies be enabled in your Web browser so that we can identify you as a repeat visitor or customer and maintain session information for logged-in users. We also use cookies to track usage trends and patterns in order to better understand and improve areas of our website.

### Personal information

We receive and store information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. When you register for an advertising account, make a booking or enquiry etc. we may ask that you provide basic contact information such as your name, phone number, address, and email address so that we can process it. We may also collect additional information at other times, including but not limited to, when you provide feedback, enter a competition, change your content or email preferences, respond to a survey, or communicate with Australias.guide customer support.

Member Profiles are password protected and all the personal information kept on our server can be checked and/or changed at any time by logging in with your Log-In credentials.

Commercial Account details are password protected, and all information kept on our server can be checked and/or changed at any time by the authorised affiliates by logging in to your company account details through the members homepage.

We may use personal information collected from you for the purpose of providing you with direct marketing material and information in the form of a newsletter. This will only apply if you have registered or subscribed to such publications by registering your details with us. However if you wish to cease receiving any such information you may let us know either by email or mail and your request will be actioned within five working days.

Individual profile and company details are not used for any other purpose. Details are only supplied to a third party supplier when it is required by law, for goods or services which you have purchased.

### Credit card and payment information

PayPal account information and/or Credit card details are only used when placing an order, and are processed by a reputable PCI compliant payment gateway, they are not stored on our servers. They are not used for any other purpose. Australias.guide utilises SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology including 128bit encryption when collecting your information.

### Security

Australias.guide strives to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our site, and periodically updates its security measures in light of current technologies.

Australias.guide is committed to the privacy and security of our clients. We will never disclose your personal details to a third party except the necessary information required by providers of products or services you have purchased.

### Links

This website contains links to other sites; these links are meant for your convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship or endorsement or approval of these sites. Please be aware that Australias.guide is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware, when they leave our site, to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

### Change in Privacy Policy

As we plan to ensure our privacy policy remains current, this policy is subject to change. Please return periodically to review our privacy policy.

### How to contact us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our use of your information, please use the contact form available HERE.
